clixtrac.com 2019-04-08

# ClixTrac - Privacy Policy

ClixTrac.com (also referred to as "we", "us" and "our"), respects the privacy of every individual who visits our website and/or uses our free banner tracking service. This statement outlines the information we will collect and how we will use that information.

This Privacy Policy will apply to your use of this website and our click tracking service. This policy statement will also instruct you on what to do if you want us to remove your personal information collected or stored during previous visits to our website.

**Personal information**  
We will not collect or retain any information about you personally (that is, your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address) unless you provide it to us voluntarily. If you register for our click tracking service, become an affiliate or ask for information by mail, we may ask you for personal information, such as, your name, mailing address, e-mail address and phone number.

In the event that you make a purchase from us, our credit card processor may ask for your credit card information, as well as, billing information.

If you do provide us with personal information during your registration, we may retain and use that information when contacting you about our service.

For example, we may use your e-mail address to send you updates about our service, such as new features that have been added or special upgrade discounts that are offered from time to time.

If you have already submitted this information and would like to remove it, you can have your email address and other registration information removed from our system by contacting us with your request. We will then close your account and remove your registration.

**Demographics and other information**  
When someone passes through our click tracking system, we may store demographic and other information about that person, such as their IP address, country, brand/version of web browser, and brand/version of operating system. This information allows our users to monitor for abuse, as well as, analyze the different demographics of their ad campaigns.

**Sharing of information with third parties**  
In the event that you place an order for some type of goods or service through our credit card processor, your order may be personally processed by that credit card processor. In these cases, all personal information required to process your order will be shared with our credit card processor, using their secure order form. Except as stated above, your personal information (name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or other information) will never be provided to any third party without your prior consent.

This third-party sharing of information does not include instances when government agencies or law enforcement require a user's information to investigate potential abuse or illegal activity.

**Security precautions**  
We are aware that you may be concerned about the privacy and confidentiality of your personal information, including, in the case of a purchase of goods or services, credit card and billing address information. Therefore, we have taken precautions to ensure that this information is safe and secure. Our credit card processor protects your transactions using a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). If your browser is capable of SSL, and most are, your sensitive information will automatically be encrypted before being sent over the Internet. You should also know that we do not store your credit card or ordering information on our server.

**Children**  
Our company does not intend to collect any personal information (such as, name, address, telephone number, age or e-mail address) from persons under eighteen years of age. If a parent or guardian of a child who has provided us with such information would like that information deleted from our records, please contact us. We will make all reasonable efforts to delete the child's information from our records.

**Cookies**  
When you view our website or click on one of our tracking links, we may store some information in the form of a "cookie" on your computer. Cookies enable us, as well as the users of our click tracking service, to track the origin of website traffic. Please be assured that our cookies are safe. They are not programs that can be used to damage files, and personal information is not gathered from them. They are used to store user, campaign and tracker IDs that help us determine which promotion a customer originated from. Our cookies have a 90 day life span.

If you do not want cookies stored on your system, most web browsers will allow you to adjust your privacy preferrences and remove prviously stored cookies from your computer's hard drive. You can usually either prevent them from being stored or trigger a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your web browser's instructions or help screen to learn more about these features.

**Links to other websites**  
We cannot ensure the protection of any personal information that you provide to a third-party website that links to or from our website. This also applies to users of our click tracking service, because those websites are owned and operated independently. Those websites may have their own separate Privacy Policy and data collection practices that are beyond our control. Any personal information that you provide to those websites will be regulated by their own Privacy Policy, if any. We can assume no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the practices, actions or policies of other websites, and cannot be responsible for the content or privacy practices of such websites.

**Acceptance of these terms**  
By using this website or our click tracking service, you agree to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this website or our service. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time. Your continued use of our website and/or service, following the posting of changes to our Privacy Policy, will signify your acceptance of those changes. Therefore, we recommend you review this Privacy Policy frequently.

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us using our contact form.
